<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Flashlight LED Torch light</string>
    <string name="first_onboard">Enjoy the bright torch and flash light with various modes and features right at your finger tips.</string>
    <string name="second_onboard">" Experience the fun of multiple colour flash light that'll transform any space into a colourful dance floor. Get started now!"</string>
    <string name="you_can_find_out_more_information_by_clicking_on_the_following_link">You can find out more information by clicking on the following link :</string>
    <string name="we_do_not_share_any_kind_of_your_personal_data_with_third_parties">We do not share any kind of your Personal Data with third parties.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_may_be_updated_from_time_to_time_for_any_reason_we_will_notify_you_of_any_changes_to_our_privacy_policy_by_posting_the_new_privacy_policy_here">Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy here.</string>
    <string name="any_type_of_modification_to_the_app_or_its_components_is_not_allowed">Any type of modification to the app or its components is not allowed.</string>
    <string name="if_we_find_the_app_is_being_used_outside_its_terms_of_use_we_may_restrict_access_to_it">If we find the app is being used outside its terms of use, we may restrict access to it.</string>
    <string name="by_pressing_the_accept_button_i_declare_i_have_read_and_accepted_the_following_condition_of_use">By pressing the Accept button, I declare I have read and accepted the following condition of use.</string>
    <string name="android_apps_is_warning_you_about_the_app_that_gives_you_many_services_and_important_information_for_safer_and_efficient_use">The application is notifying you to the presence of an app that provides several services that are essential information for safer and more efficient use.</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions"><u>Terms &amp; Conditions</u></string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_tv"><u>Privacy Policy</u></string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_cap">Terms of Use</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="guide1">How to remove this application from the restricted list of power saving features on the phone?</string>
    <string name="guide2">Why this app not flashing or not flashing sometimes?</string>
    <string name="guide3">How to avoid accidentally closing this app?</string>
    <string name="guide4">What permissions does this app require?</string>
    <string name="second_question">1. This application was accidentally
        \n2. On some phones, the phone\'s battery optimizer did not allow the app to run in the background, causing this app to stop working.
        \n3. When the phone indicators low battery level and you activate the power saving feature, this application may stop working.
        \n4. When you shutdown and restart your phone, on some devices this app may not be able to restart itself.
        \n5. In any case, when this application is closed and not working, you just need to reopen this application.</string>
    <string name="third_question">Locking this app on the multitasking manager can make this app work better, keep it active all the time, avoid this app being closed accidentally (disabled and inoperable).</string>
    <string name="fourth_question">Call management: Enable this permission, when you having incoming calls, we can flash to notify you Notifications: Enable this permission so that we can notify battery status Background running: Enable this permission to keep the flash of incoming call and battery detection working stably Notification Access: Enable this permission so that we can flash when you receive messages from other applications Display Permission: Enable this permission so that we can show notifications appear on the top of screen Camera Access: Enable this permission so that flashlight can work normally.</string>
    <string name="turn_incoming">Turn On For Incoming Calls</string>
    <string name="turn_sms">Turn On For SMS</string>
    <string name="turn_notification"><![CDATA[Turn On Notifications]]></string>
    <string name="on">On</string>
    <string name="off">Off</string>
    <string name="cannot_access_camera">Cannot access camera, is it being used by another app?</string>
    <string name="no_camera">No camera</string>
    <string name="milliseconds_format">%d milliseconds\n</string>

</resources>